Hello Hello Friends, today I have brought to you
an excellent product of Star Health Insurance Company named Young
Star Plan, which if you are a Polytechnic College
or less than a husband, then you
can take this product now, so friends let's
start with
these special features,
you get temple run renewal discount for
lifelong if you take this policy,
after that there are different premium payment options
in it, if you have taken a quarter
then take it and give notice of it,
what does A Naughty P mean, whatever
TP is there in it, it is this, okay next thing is
that cashless facility available, balance
discount and you get
that additional
pre-existing disease, if you
tell the company that you have this disease and
take the policy, then the company says that we will
cover your pre-existing disease after one year
and specific diseases which include
piles, hernia, gastroenterology, cyst and nose,
ear, throat surgery, all these are included
which come under specific diseases.  This is
news after one year in our youngster product.
Now let us move ahead to the type of cover. In this you
can take individual policy as well as
family floater policy. No
validity if your age is a teen or more than 40
but less than 40 then you can take this one
and dependent
children can be from 3 months to 25 years in this
you can take your own policy or
your wife's policy or a
nearby policy and you can have maximum three children.
Your net plans run
in reverse repo and mid term inclusion is
available for newly married couples, new
born baby is required. All these
features are available.
After that we will talk further about the review and for
how long term you can take this policy.
You can take this policy for 3 lakh, 5 lakh,
10 lakh, 15 lakh, 20 lakh or you
can take this policy up to one crore.
Type of Boys Payment Option: As I
told you earlier also, there are two types of plans in this,
Silver and  The second is Gold and payment option
in this, it is group, quarterly, half yearly. Let's move ahead and see that there is no
company medical checkup in this plan. Now we will talk about the primary cover in
which road ambulance is also covered.
Air ambulance is also covered in this product.
All the points covered in the Young Stars product.
Next cycle, now we will talk about
health checkup.
Its friend friend Young Sir plan is a
plan which is completely different from all other plans.
What happens in all other plans is that
if you take a claim, then you
cannot take a health checkup in that plan. But
in Youngsters Players, whether you have taken a claim
or not, it is fine and if your
policy is five, then you
can take a health checkup in the family floater for Rs. 3000
and in individual you can take it for Rs. 2000. The
bigger your policy, the
more you can get a health checkup done. Let's
move ahead and
now we will talk about the cost of health checkup
expenses. These towards the cost of
health check up to the limit mentioned in the temple built upon.
Completion of policy are
provided health checkup Eastern Airtel
network facility as I
told you that if you take a policy of 5 lakhs
then the cost of health checkup is ₹2000 and for family
₹3000 so if you
go to any network hospital then you
can get the health checkup done
hands free of cost which will be completely
cashless and if you do not go in cash then you will get
reimbursed that next
point Android phablet
can get the policy renewed okay
after that payment inside the
benefit does not form part of the basic
summit this is for all of you friends
and tenth utilize the mountain the benefit cannot be carried
forward hint things you
know so maximum limit for this
benefit not exceed limit applicable for
the new renewal
that is a friend let's go ahead and automatic
restoration support your policy is of 5 lakhs
and all your money gets exhausted
in any claim and  If you make a second claim that year, the
company tells you that
we will
restore 100% of the problems in your policy that year. If
your sports policy is of 5 lakhs, then after one year if you
claim on your policy,
if your 5 lakhs get exhausted, then the amount will be
restored again. So we
can say that our policy is of
10 lakhs instead of 5 lakhs. Let's move ahead
friends, for
example, five lucky policies worth 5 lakhs.
Now let's move ahead friends, friends,
NCB clip bonus, okay friends,
this is what happens in every plane,
no claim bonus, okay friends, it goes up to 100
%, to the same joint
maximum. In this airplane, you
get 2020 percent every year, okay,
so let's
go to the net and ask for an example,
next year
's five lucky policies are yours and first Salim did
not make his claim, that policy got separated as per 20%,
okay, so it is 5
lakhs, one lakh jobs got plus  Restoration
policy behind the policy goes to 11
from next year
that medical friends and if you do not take this for 5 years
continuously then by bringing it to clean stop the
policy will be of 15 lakhs ok so
friends let's move ahead that if there is a
road traffic accident then
friends in this the accident is caused
by day seven basic injury
salary increase by 25% which is the main
sports policy of 5 lakhs
and in this
I example
that your policy was of 5 lakhs restore 5000
and road traffic accidents tiger as
I told you then you please
[music]
subscribe premium gets subscribe
602 and subscribe to the
gold line features so friend this
gold plan has two main features first
maternity cover second hospital cash is
given 3000
till today maximum two deliveries should
be there and hospital cash sheds are given
but now to do maximum 2011 policy
after half an hour now you get scan ad when
School and you click on continue Tax
Benefit ID ok
and if you face any problem you
can call on this number also on the helpline number of Star and I have
also displayed my private number below, this is my
number, if you call on this then friends thank
you this was a very
good policy of Star Health youngsters
friends see taking a policy is not a big deal
but claim handling is the back I am
talking to Singh Johal only manager
if you have any problem in taking a policy
if you have a policy running in any other company
then you can contact me
this is my number 80 six you can call on this
and subscribe to the appointment number
thank you friends thank you